{
    "id": "0d3839cf0ca44ffc83127e6817e3d44e",
    "title": "Would vs. Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Alice …………………… arrive soon. She left office at",
            "description": "We use should to indicate logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c56cf0d1ebd4797af3f96e587cacd64"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I carry this bag?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion or to offer help.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b1a7b0426dbe430ab32ad4b07d52e40a"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………………. be invited to the party.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43c14aef03cf466ca2f79084d1d52cdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone ……………………….. abide by the law.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f68ebabcabf4ecc97febb279c8bf226"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… waste your time or money.",
            "description": "Shouldn't can be used to forbid. ",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "shouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0ebc27eec4544dd8b47b2ed1f796b58"
        },
        {
            "question": "She promised that she ………………………….. help.",
            "description": "Would is the past tense of will in reported speech.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38ae614a7339421e97d55383d9a44c40"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be able to come.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12b5789ec09f4d8286b827e563450261"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like some more rice?",
            "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d2eb65c94d964950996a86c9914aea44"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. I report this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5841220c6aac4547a1bb6519cbf1e0e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew that I …………………………… work harder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e4c600dc26a42ed86ad71a7c821c7a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………….. have told them about my plans.",
            "description": "Should not have is used to criticize people for doing things. ",
            "answers": [
                "shouldn't",
                "wouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "294b9092d5ac4fce91cb6f08a459d63b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have insulted him.",
            "description": "Should not have is used to criticize people for doing things. ",
            "answers": [
                "shouldn't",
                "wouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "67d04405374d446ea5f5f42756be99c0"
        }
    ]
}